Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Audiovisuals, 1993-2004; Undated; 11
  - Videocassette Tapes, VHS, 1993-2004; Undated; 11.3
    - "Partial Birth Abortion", Nightline Show WABC, Undated (Video-tape 85)
    - "Pataki for Governor", Nassau Suffolk State, 1:30:00, Undated (Video-tape 86)
    - "Pataki Spots", West East Central Nassau Suffolk State, 3:00:00, Undated (Video-tape 87)
    - "Peas In A Pod", London for Governor Commercial, Undated (Video-tape 88)
    - "Road to City Hall", NY1 New York Market, 2001 March 06 (Video-tape 89)
    - "Schumer's Shame", O'Grady For Senate, Undated (Video-tape 90)
    - "See Your Doctor", New York State Conservative Party, :30, 2000 September 15 (Video-tape 91)
    - "See Your Doctor", New York State Conservative Party, :30, 2000 September 19 (Video-tape 92)
    - "Segment Featuring Michael Long", News, 5:00, 2000 February 28 (Video-tape 93)
    - "Segments Featuring Rudy Giuliani & Michael Long", Undated (Video-tape 94)
    - "Silent", New York State Conservative Party, :30, 1996 February 29 (Video-tape 95)
    - "Snapshots", New York State Conservative Party, :30, 2000 May 26 (Video-tape 96)
    - "Snapshots", New York State Conservative Party, :30, 2000 June 02 (Video-tape 97)
    - "Special Report with Brit Hume", FNC National Cable Market, 2:50, 2000 April 14 (Video-tape 98)
    - "The Conservative Century" ACU, Undated (Video-tape 99)
    - "The Conservative Next Door", New York Conservative Party, 1994 October 11 (Video-tape 100)
    - "The Conservative Next Door", New York Conservative Party, Undated (Video-tape 101)
    - "The Conservative Next Door", New York Conservative Party, Undated (Video-tape 102)
    - "The Conservative Party", Silent & Compassion, 1:00:00, 1996 February 27 (Video-tape 102)
    - "The Incredible Shrinking Billionaire", New York State Conservative Party, :30, Undated (Video-tape 103)
    - "The Incredible Shrinking Billionaire" New York State Conservative Party, :30, Undated (Video-tape 104)
    - "The Open Mind", Dr. Anne A. Paolucci, 1998 September 15 (Video-tape 105)
    - "The Perfect Liberal Couple", O'Grady for Senate, Undated (Video-tape 106)
    - "The Ten O' Clock News", WNYW New York Market, 2:35, 2000 April 14 (Video-tape 107)
    - "Truth", National Smokers Alliance, :30, 2000 January 26 (Video-tape 108)
    - "Welfare", NY Conservative Party NYCP TV, :10, 1994 October 08 (Video-tape 109)
    - "Welfare Perks Taxes", New York Conservative Party, 1994 October 10 (Video-tape 110)
    - "Winning with Ideas, The Incredible Shrinking Billionaire", New York Conservative Party, 1:00:00, 2002 October 18 (Video-tape 111)
    - "Yankee Baby", American Conservative Union, 2000 September 08 (Video-tape 112)